Theresa Seay papers, Inclusive: 1865-2008, undated, Bulk: 1960-2002
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
Theresa Seay papers
Inclusive: 1865-2008, undated, Bulk: 1960-2002
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
55
Seay, Theresa
18 archival boxes.
The Theresa Seay papers consist of a dissertation written by Seay, research materials and articles written by Seay and articles collected by Theresa Seay, pertaining to the assassination of John F. Kennedy.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Excellent.
Biography/Profile
Theresa Margaret Carroll Seay was born in New York City on August 28, 1943, the only child of Charles Edward Carroll and Stephania Klapik Carroll. Charles died when Theresa was six years old and she was raised by her mother. She was educated through high school in Catholic schools graduating from Notre Dame High School near the top of her class.
Theresa attended Washington State College in Machias, Maine, until the end of her sophomore year when she transferred to the University of Maine at Orono. She graduated with a bachelor's degree in history and education in 1965, and then attended graduate school for one semester.
She met and married Kenneth Edward Garnett in 1968 and settled near Ellsworth, Maine. They lived there for about 10 years. Their only child, David Edward, was born in 1973. During this time, she joined Mensa. Theresa worked for 10 years as a veterinary assistant in Ellsworth. She also bred German Shepherd dogs, Arabian horses, and operated a riding stable. She was active in local politics, although she never ran for office. At some point Theresa became interested in JFK assassination research. After studying the available information, she became an advocate for alternate explanations. She also, with her Mensa network, took part in demonstrations about injustices she encountered.
After a divorce, she and son David moved to Raleigh, North Carolina. In the Raleigh Mensa group, she met and subsequently married Robert Seay, an engineer at a local manufacturer of electronic components. She became a prominent member in this local Mensa group.
In 1988 Theresa and Robert moved to Asheville, North Carolina, where she set up a consulting
business. During the three years in Asheville, she wrote several articles and stories, some of which were published in various specialty magazines. She attended several conferences of JFK researchers and chaired one in Dallas on the 30th anniversary in 1993.
After moving to Connecticut, Theresa entered the graduate program at Western Connecticut University in Danbury in 1993. She finished the master's program there and was admitted to the University of Connecticut at Storrs for her doctoral studies. She was awarded her Ph.D. in History and Government in 2002. Her dissertation was about the discrepancies in the medical evidence between Parkland Hospital and the Bethesda autopsy of JFK.
After the 9-11 terrorist attacks, Theresa joined a local group of researchers where she put considerable effort into investigating and communicating with other colleagues. She continued this activity until her death on May 22, 2011.
Scope and Content
In my thesis I intend to prove that the single bullet theory is totally without foundation and contrary to known facts and reason. Moreover, the [Warren] Commission knew it at the time and deliberately withheld evidence which would have negated their conclusions. -Theresa Seay, Thesis Proposal
The Theresa Seay Papers combine over thirty years of research in the assassination of John F. Kennedy. The result of which included a master’s thesis, a PhD dissertation, a newsletter run, and speaking engagements. Her research is rooted in the volumes of the Warren Commission, the House Select Committee on Assassinations, and numerous documents released by the FBI, CIA and other federal agencies since 1963. Seay amassed a large collection of books related to the Kennedy Assassination, a selection of which are included in the collection. Major topics include Kennedy assassination literature, conspiracies and cover-ups, the CIA and the FBI.
Materials are arranged topically: Conferences, Correspondence, Dissertation, Publications, Research, and Media.
Arrangement
The papers were previously arranged in 2013 in an order that has been largely maintained with minor rearrangements. Several books are included in two boxes at the end of the collection. A VHS tape, a film reel, and a couple floppy disks are also included.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 55. Acquired 2012-02-10
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963 -- Assassination.; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald),1917-1963.; Kennedy, Robert F., 1925-1968.; Oswald, Lee Harvey.
Subjects (Organizations)
United States. Warren Commission.
Subjects
Conspiracy theories.
Genres
Books.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Manuscripts.; Newsletters.
- Conferences, 1992-1994, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Excellent.
  Biography/Profile
  Theresa Seay was an expert on the Warren Commission report and attended and was invited to speak at many conferences during her active research years. This material is from conference attended between 1992-1994.
  - Web of Conspiracy, General, 1992 October 17-18 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Kennedy Assassination Conference, General, 1992 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Second Research Conference of the Third Decade, Article, 1993 June 18-20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Second Research Conference of the Third Decade, General, 1993 June 18-20 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Second Research Conference of the Third Decade, Cutler, 1993 June 18-20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Second Research Conference of the Third Decade, Presentations, 1993 June 18-20 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Second Research Conference of the Third Decade, Zapruder Film, 1993 June 18-20 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Association of Professional and Analytical Researchers, General, 1993 August 27-29 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Teach-In and Symposium on the 30th Anniversary of the Assassination of President JFK, General, 1993 November 12-14 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Teach-In and Symposium on the 30th Anniversary of the Assassination of President JFK, Publicity, 1993 November 12-14 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Teach-In and Symposium on the 30th Anniversary of the Assassination of President JFK, Photos, 1993 November 12-14 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Assassination Symposium on JFK, Photos, 1993 November 18-22 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Assassination Symposium on JFK, General, 1993 November 18-22 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Assassination Symposium on JFK, Dallas Wrap-Up, 1993 November 18-22 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Assassination Symposium on JFK (ASK), General, 1994 November 18-22 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Three Decades of Doubt, General, 1994 October 7-10 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Three Decades of Doubt, National Archives, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Three Decades of Doubt, Coalition on Political Assassination, 1994 March-October (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1973-1996, undated; 2
  The Correspondence series contains items related to her research and other various interests.
  - Assassination Information Bureau, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Assassination Records Review Board, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - “Back Channels” Newsletter, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Citizens Commission of Inquiry, 1977 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Political Assassinations, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Congressional Investigations, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - House Select Committee on Assassinations, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Lesar, Jim (Assassination Archives and Research Center), 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 25A)
  - Letter to the Editor, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - McCarthy, Eugene, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Mensa, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Presidents, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Press Release, 1977, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Other Researchers, 1973-1979, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Representative William Cohen, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Requests, 1975-2004 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Senator William D. Hathaway, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Television, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Thank You Notes, 1977-1995 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - World Watches International, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Dissertation, 1993-2002, undated; 3
  The Dissertation series contains manuscripts of her writings, as well as paperwork needed to get it approved and published.
  - Pages IV-VI, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Introduction, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Chapter 1, Chapter 2, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 3, Chapter 4, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 5, Chapter 6, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 7, Chapter 8, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 9, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Selected Bibliography, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Award, 2001 October (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Chapter Edits, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Defense, 2002 April 4 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Defense Notes, 2002 April 4 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Disks, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School Guidelines, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Illustrations (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Illustrations (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Northern Illinois University Press, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Palgrave Publishing, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Permissions, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Prospectus, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Publishing, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - University of Connecticut, 1994-2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Western State Connecticut University, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Research, 1865-2002, undated; 4
  The Research series contain materials from the Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), news clippings, the National Archive, the Warren Commission, and the US House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA).
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), ARRB, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Acoustics, 1994-2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Advertisement, 1963 February 18 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), AFIP Compliance, 1997 June 12 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Audio Tapes, 1995 December 12 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, 1963 December 6 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, 1963 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, 1963 November 26 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, 1992 May-October (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy Inventory, 1996 March 15 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy Photographs, 1967 February (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy Physicians, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy Protocol, 1963 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy Protocol, 1963 November 24 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy Witness, 1963 November 23 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, Baxter, Charles, 1963 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, Bullet, 1963 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, Casket, 1963 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, Death Certificate, 1963 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, Film/X-Ray Receipt, 1963 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, Gawler’s Funeral Home, 1963 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, Hutton, Patricia, 1963 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, Jenkins, Marion, 1963 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, Jones, Ronald, 1963 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, Missile Removed, 1963 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, Navy X-Ray Technologies, 1963 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Autopsy, Transcript, 1963 November 22 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Ballistics, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Baxter, Charles, 1964 March 24 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Bell, Audrey, 1997 April (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Benson, Leland, 1977 August 16 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Bone Fragment Search, 1996 November (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Boring, Floyd, 1996 September 19 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Boswell, J. Thornton, 1977 August (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Boswell, J. Thornton, 1996 February 26 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Bouck, Robert, 1977 September 6 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Bouck, Robert, 1978 August 18 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Bouck, Robert, 1996 April 30 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Boyajian, Roger, 1997 September 5 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Burkley, George, 1963 November 24 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Burkley, George, 1967 October 17 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Burkley, George [Son], 1997 January 10 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Burkley, Richard, 1997 January 10 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Carrico, Charles, 1964 March 25 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Casket, 1964 March 19 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Casket, 1965 February and 1965 September (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Cau, Eve [Patricia Eve Walkling], 1996 November 26 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Cauico, James, 1978 January 11 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Certificate of Death, 1963 December 6 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), CIA, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Clark Panel Report, 1968 February 26 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Clark, William Kemp, 1964 March 21 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Collins Radio, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Correspondence, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Crenshaw, Charles, 1997 April 14 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Custer, Jerrol, 1980 October (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Custer, Jerrol, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Custer, Jerrol, 1992 August 31 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Custer, Jerrol, 1997 October 28 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Custer, Jerrol F., 1997 September - October (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), David, Dennis, 1997 February 6 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Davis, Richard, 1997 March 6 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Denlea, Nancy [Daughter of George Buckley], 1997 January 13 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Deposition, 1998 August 27 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), FBI Memo, 1963 November 26 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), FBI Memos, 1964 March 16 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Finck, Pierre, 1963 December (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Finck, Pierre, 1965 January (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Finck, Pierre, 1995 December 19 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Finck, Pierre, 1996 April-May (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Fox, James, 1978 August 7 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Gawler’s Funeral Home, 1963 November 25 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Gerald Ford, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Government Mistrust, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Groden, Robert, 1996 July 2 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Grossman, Robert, 1997 March 21 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Hagan, Joseph, 1996 May 5 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Harper Jack, 1977 August 17 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), House Select Committee on Assassination (HSCA) Executive Session, 1978 August 11 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Humes, James, 1963 November 23-24 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Humes, James, 1964 March 16 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Humes, James, 1992 October 7 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Humes, James J. (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Humes, James J. (2 of 2), 1996 February 13 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Interviews, 1964 March 12 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Jackie Kennedy, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Jenkins, James, 1977 August 29 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Jenkins, Marion, 1964 March 25 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Jenkins, Marion, 1977 November 10 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), JFK Conspiracy, 1998-2001 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Karnei, Jr., Robert, 1977 August 29 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Karnei, Jr., Robert, 1996 April 29 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Kellerman, Roy, 1977 August 24-25 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Kellerman, Roy H., 1964 March 9 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Knudsen, Gloria, 1996 May 7 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Lifton, David, 1966 November (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Lipsey, Richard, 1978 January 18 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Research, Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Livingston, Robert, 1993 November 19 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Research, Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Lloyd, Kathy, 1996 October 4 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Louisiana v. Clay Shaw, 1969 February (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Madonia, Vince, 1996 June 25 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Mastrovito, James M., 1997 April 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Materials, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), McClelland, Robert, 1964 March 25 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), McDonald, Earl, 1996 May 14 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Media Inquiries, 1966 June-October (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Medical Evidence, 1963 November 26 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Medical Exhibits, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Medical Panel Meeting, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Meetings, 1995 February-June (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), National Archives, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Research, Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), National Archives, 1977 September 6 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), National Naval Medical Center Compliance, 1997 June 27 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), News Releases, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), News Releases, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), News Releases, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), News Releases, 1998 January-September (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), O’Connor, Paul, 1977 August 25 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), O’Donnell, Joe, 1997 January-February (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), O’Neill, Jr., Frances, 1978 January 1 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), O’Neill, Jr., Francis X., 1997 September 12 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Perry, Malcolm, 1964 March 25 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Perry, Malcolm, 1964 January 11 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Peters, Conrad, 1964 March 24 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), President John F. Kennedy Assassination records Collection Act of 1992, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Reed, Edward, 1979 November 25 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Reed, Edward, 1992 March 16 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Reed, Edward, 1997 September-October (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Reibe, Floyd, 1978 March (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Reibe, Floyd, 1979 November 11 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Reibe, Floyd, 1989 July (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Reibe, Floyd, 1997 April-May (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB), Rhoads, James B., 1997 March 11 (Box 6, Folder 11)